(relaxed country-rock music)
♪ We're caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you too much,
baby ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Why can't you see ♪
♪ What you're doing to me ♪
♪ When you don't believe a word
I say? ♪
♪ We can't go on together ♪
♪ With suspicious minds ♪
♪ And we can't build our dreams♪
♪ On suspicious minds ♪
♪ So if an old friend I know ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Stops by to say hello ♪
♪ Would I still see
suspicion in your eyes? ♪
♪ But here we go again ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ Asking where I've been ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ You can't see the tears
are real, I'm cryin ♪
♪ Yes, I'm cryin ♪
♪ We can't go on together ♪
♪ With suspicious minds ♪
♪ Suspicious minds ♪
♪ And we can't build our dreams♪
♪ On suspicious minds ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Oh, let our love survive ♪
♪ I'll dry the tears from your
eyes ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Let's don't let a good thing
die ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ When honey, you know I've
never ♪
♪ Lied to you ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Mmm-mm yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ We're caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Because I love you too much,
baby ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Why can't you see ♪
♪ What you're doin' to me ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ When you don't believe a word
I say? ♪
♪ Well, don't you know I'm ♪
♪ Caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Because I love you too much,
baby ♪
♪ Well, don't you know I'm ♪
♪ Caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Because I love you too much,
baby ♪
♪ Well, don't you know I'm ♪
♪ Caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
(air whooshes)
♪ Because I love you too much,
baby ♪
(dramatic piano music)
(Elvis grunting)
(bright music)
(audience applauds)
(audience cheers)